all right what do you picture when your
sve u redu šta ti sliku kada
picture wireless earbuds these are the
slike bežične slušalice za uši su to
ones I've been using for years okay
koje sam koristio godinama u redu
there's some that Wireless there
postoje neki koji Wireless tamo
bluetooth oh yeah they connect to my
bluetooth oh yeah oni povezati to moj
phone or my mp3 player right and when I
ili moj mp3 plejer
when I'm jogging cuz I jog right that's
kada sam trčanje jer sam trčim u pravu da je to
what I do
Sta ja radim
obviously right what do they do in your
očigledno je u redu šta rade u vašem
job they stay in the cable this thing
posao ostaje u kablu
here it's got a little bit of a weight
ovde ima malo težine
to it and it will actually pull that out
i to će zapravo izvući
of my ear and it's like ah it's
mog uha i to je kao da je to
frustrating as you say it's not quite
frustrirajuće kao što kažete da nije sasvim
Wireless they're great right these are
Bežični sjajni su u pravu su
great but they're not quite wireless
odličan, ali nisu baš bežični
tonight we're gonna be introducing you
Večeras ćemo vas upoznati
to Joe visas new product line we've got
Joeovim vizama imamo novu liniju proizvoda
the shield we've got the beat winds I'm
u štitu koji imamo u udarnim vetrovima
going to show you the difference between
pokazaću vam razliku između
them they are the first the only the
oni su oni prvi jedini
best fully wireless earbuds I'm talking
najbolje potpuno bežične slušalice koje pričam
over the moon about this think about
o Mjesecu o tome razmislite
this wireless in your ears none of this
ovo bežično u vašim ušima ništa od ovoga
and wireless charging perfect let's take
i bežično punjenje savršen uzmimo
a look here we go
a izgledaju idemo
ah this is the box for the shield this
ah ovo je kutija za štit
is the box for the B twins now why have
je kutija za B blizance sada zašto
we got both well they are there's a
imamo i jedno i drugo dobro je da postoji
little bit of a difference in price
malo razlike u cijeni
we're going to talk a little bit about
pričat ćemo malo o tome
that but essentially these are similar
to je, ali u suštini , slično
devices they're ear buds right so if
Uređaji koji imaju ušne štipaljke tako da ako
you've got somebody who's an audiophile
imaš nekoga ko je audiofil
fan of music on your Christmas list
ljubitelj muzike na božićnoj listi
these are what you want to be looking at
to je ono što želite da gledate
first of all we're gonna look at the
prvo ćemo pogledati
shield now both of these there there are
štit sada oboje postoji
some real similarities between them okay
neke prave sličnosti između njih su u redu
Sasha
Sasha
both of these are truly wireless I'm
oba su zaista bežična Ja sam
talking no wires you're gonna see how
ne pričajući žice koje ćete videti kako
that is accomplished in just a couple of
to se postiže za samo nekoliko
moments also both of them have been nano
trenutke i obojica su nano
coated do you know what that means no
obložena, znate li što to znači ne
that means that if you are using these
to znači da ako ih koristite
for workouts if you're jogging if you're
za treninge ako trčite ako ste
at the gym if you're doing your jumping
u teretani ako radite skakanje
jacks or jump squats uh-huh if you're
jacks ili jump squats uh-huh ako si ti
sweating you're not gonna have to worry
znojenje ti nećeš morati da brineš
about your earbuds basically you know I
o svojim slušalicama u osnovi znate
don't think they would call them
nemojte misliti da će ih zvati
waterproof but you don't have to worry
vodootporan, ali ne morate brinuti
about sweat that's for sure so they are
o znoju koji je sigurno tako
absolutely sweat proof they're gonna
apsolutno dokaz o znoju oni će
work for you you're not gonna have a
Rad za tebe nećeš imati
problem with that so both of these are
problem sa tim, tako da su oba ova
like that they're both wireless they're
kao da su oba bežična
both you know they're essentially
oboje znate da su u suštini
similar devices with a couple of
sličnih uređaja sa nekoliko
differences between them we're gonna
razlike između njih ćemo
show ya so let's get into the shield and
pokažite se tako da uđemo u štit i
this one goes for $79.99 now this week
ovo ide za $ 79.99 sada ove nedelje
for cyber week it's on sale for just
za sajber nedelju je na prodaju za samo
$59.99 so just a heads up for you and
$ 59.99 tako da samo glavu gore za vas i
there you go so that's what's in the box
eto, tako da je ono što je u kutiji
so you see that we've got some kind of
tako da vidite da imamo neku vrstu
behind the ear hanging things these are
iza uva viseće stvari
going to help if you are really roughing
će vam pomoći ako ste stvarno grubi
it if you're you know jogging through
ako znate da trčite
the forest or something like that you're
šuma ili nešto slično ti
doing something that you really want to
radiš nešto što stvarno želiš
make sure that they're gonna stay on
pobrini se da ostanu
your ear but these are entirely optional
Vaše uho, ali ovo je potpuno opcionalno
now the earbuds themselves this is the
sada sami bubice ovo je
jeebies shield just see if I can get one
jeebies štit samo vidjeti ako ja mogu dobiti jedan
out here
ovde
there we go that's all there is to it oh
Evo ga, to je sve
that's sharp
to je oštro
that's our left ear and let's get it out
to je naše levo uho i izvadimo ga
here don't worry you only got to do this
ovde se ne brinite da ćete to samo uraditi
once folks there get underneath and pop
kada se ljudi popnu i pop
it out there we are so there's our two
tamo smo mi, tako da su naša dva
ears how do you like that now both sets
uši kako vam se sviđaju sada oba seta
of these jobbies ear buds have just
od ovih radnih aparata samo su uši
simple touch controls and they do
jednostavne kontrole dodirom i one to rade
support things that you know what you
podržite stvari koje znate što vi
would expect from a bluetooth earbud
očekivao bih od bluetooth slušalice
these days like being able to make and
Ovih dana kao što je sposobnost da se napravi i
take calls being able to control your
uzimajte pozive da biste mogli da kontrolišete svoje
phone let's make sure I've got the right
telefon da budemo sigurni da imam pravo
ear here do they have very nice you just
Uho ovdje imaju vrlo lijepo samo vi
talked to me oh it did yeah we'll get
Razgovarali su sa mnom, oh, jeste
into the sizing in just a moment so
u određivanje veličine u samo jednom trenutku
these ones this is the shield and I can
ovi ovi su štit i ja mogu
hear that it's kind of muted the sound
čujem da je to nekako prigušilo zvuk
in here so that's what they look like on
ovdje, tako da izgledaju ovako
me and that's just pushed into my ear
i to mi je samo gurnuto u uho
there's no behind the ear strap there's
tamo nema trake za uši
nothing going behind my head there's
tamo ništa ne ide iza moje glave
nothing hanging but beneath my chin
ništa nije visilo nego pod mojom bradom
there you have it so how did they charge
Eto ga imate , kako su oni naplatili
that's the question you see these little
to je pitanje koje vi vidite malo
proprietary little ports they look like
vlasnički mali portovi koji izgledaju
and I said they're Wireless right I
i ja sam rekao da su bežični pravu ja
promised you that let's take a look at
obećao sam vam da pogledamo
how this thing works this is one of
kako ova stvar radi ovo je jedna od
those innovations that I love from Jabez
one inovacije koje volim od Jabez-a
now we saw something similar with the
sada smo videli nešto slično sa
last set of job easier buds that we
poslednji set posla lakšim pupoljcima koji smo mi
looked at and if you're hard-of-hearing
pogledao sam i ako ste teško čuli
if you've got hearing problems you want
ako želiš probleme sa sluhom
to check those ones out there called the
za provjeru one tamo zove
jeebies amp sound you can actually check
Jeebies amp zvuk koji možete provjeriti
those ones out at cat5 dot TV slash amp
one na cat5 dot TV slash amp
sound what they do differently is they
zvuče ono što rade drugačije su oni
also act as hearing aids so we kind of
također djeluje kao slušni aparat tako da smo nekako
saw this technology but this is
video ovu tehnologiju, ali ovo je
the evolution of that without the
evolucija toga bez
hearing aid component these are
komponente slušnog pomagala su to
specifically from use that can and calls
posebno od upotrebe koje mogu i poziva
but let's get into the accessories all
ali budimo u pribor sve
right we've got a wire I told you it was
da imamo žicu koju sam vam rekao
Wireless don't you worry I'll show you
Bežični ne brinite, pokazat ću vam
how it works
kako radi
now that's all that's in the box we've
to je sve što je u kutiji
got a little carrying case now we
Imam malo torbica sada smo
remember Joby's is very innovative with
Zapamtite da je Jobijev veoma inovativan
their carrying cases what do we notice
njihove torbe za nošenje što primećujemo
we've got a USB input on the case no USB
imamo USB ulaz na kućištu bez USB-a
input on the earbuds themselves but when
sami ulaz na slušalice, ali kada
you put the earbuds into the case which
stavite slušalice u kućište koje
is a nice hard shell protective case
je lijepa torbica od tvrdog oklopa
right
pravo
they magnetically suck themselves into
Magnetno se usisavaju
the case into the right spot you push
slučaj na pravo mjesto gdje gurate
the power button and those babies are
dugme za uključivanje i onih bebe
charging look put that away put it in
punjenje izgled put da ga stavi u
your pocket it's really really tiny
Vaš džep je zaista jako mali
there you have it and then when you're
tu imate i onda kada ste
ready to use them there you go
spremni da ih iskoristite tamo
so both sets of earbuds are going to
tako da su oba seta bubice će
last for three hours if you're listening
traje tri sata ako slušate
to music for hours if you're making them
muziku satima ako ih čini
taking calls and standby is a whopping
uzimanje poziva i stanje pripravnosti je ogroman
50 hours okay so there you have it you
50 sati u redu, tako da ga imate
asked about sizing size yes all right no
pitao za veličinu veličine da, u redu ne
problem there we've got two different
problem tamo imamo dva različita
types of what do you call these like
vrste onoga što vi nazivate ovakvim
in-ear adapt doors to make it fit you
prilagodite vrata u uho kako bi vam odgovarala
more snugly we've got little itty bitty
više smo usko povezani
tiny ones for the tiny ears and we've
sitne za male uši i mi
got some larger kind of circular shape
dobio neki veći oblik kružnog oblika
ones these ones are more or oval like
one te oni su više ili ovalne kao
and then we've got a couple other little
a onda imamo još par malih
things here these are like sweat seals
stvari ovde su kao pečati znoj
and little pegs that you can plug in
i male kvačice koje možete uključiti
where the behind the ear component which
gde iza ušne komponente koja
we looked at over here
pogledali smo ovde
thanks guys here when we're not using
hvala momcima ovde kada ne koristimo
these we can actually put one of these
ovo mi zapravo možemo staviti jedan od ovih
pegs into the hole so that it keeps any
klinovi u rupu, tako da ih zadržava
water or moisture out of that there we
vode ili vlage od toga tu smo
go so that's how I'd probably want to
idi tako da bih ja to želela
use it okay oh I love that so that is
upotrebi ga u redu o da volim to
the jeebies shield again
opet jebid štit
$79.99 and they're on sale this week for
$ 79.99 i oni su na prodaju ove nedelje
cyber week for 59.99 so let's get into
cyber sedmica za 59.99, pa hajde da uđemo
the be twins these are japaese be twins
Biti blizanci su japanski blizanci
now a little bit different here you can
sada malo drugačije Ovdje možete
see different presentation a little bit
vide različite prezentacije malo
of a step up in that regard let's
u tom smislu, hajde
actually get right in there and get a
ustvari odmah stignemo i dobijemo
look at the B twins now they're clips
pogledaj B blizance sada su klipovi
are in fact in the ear clips so these
u stvari su u isječcima za uši, tako da je ovo
actually go into the inside of your ear
zapravo uđite u unutrašnjost vašeg uha
they don't go around the back of your
ne idu okolo sa zadnje strane
ear a little bit different and what I
uho malo drugačije i ono što ja
notice here that you may not notice at
ovdje obavijestite da nećete primijetiti
home
Dom
as far as difference goes is that the
što se tiče razlika ide je u tome što
shield are made of plastic a nice
štit je od plastike lijep
durable plastic with the coating however
izdržljiva plastika sa premazom
these are aluminum they have a really
to su aluminijum, oni zaista imaju
good you know the the whole design of
dobro znate cijeli dizajn
Jimmy's products are fantastic I love
Jimmyjevi proizvodi su fantastični i volim
these but there you go so how do these
ovo, ali evo kako to radite
fit in my ear let's just kind of get a
uklopim se u moje uho, hajdemo samo dobiti
look here how do these differ from the
pogledajte kako se oni razlikuju od
shield they lighter weight they look
štiti ih manje težine
like perhaps they are super lightweight
možda su super lagani
so I'm just pushing this little guy up
pa samo guram ovog malog
in here and it just kind of clips in you
ovde i to je samo neka vrsta klipova u tebi
feel that area of your ear it just goes
osetite to područje vašeg uha samo što ide
right in there these are definitely
tamo su definitivno
manly ones right pink there you go so
Pravi ružičasti tamo idete tako
that's what they look like this is the B
tako izgleda da je ovo B
twins
blizanci
so the B twins also have an upgraded
tako da i B blizanci imaju nadograđenu
sound driver so the speaker themselves
zvuk vozač tako da sam zvučnik
are higher-end and again they are an
su veći-end i ponovo oni su
aluminum bodied ear but these also have
aluminijumski uho, ali i oni imaju
another unique feature Sasha again they
još jedna jedinstvena osobina Sashe ponovo
are completely wireless there is no wire
potpuno su bežične nema žice
going between them and the B twins in
ide između njih i B blizanaca u
fact act as two separate Bluetooth
Činjenica je da su dva odvojena Bluetootha
devices so your left and right ear are
uređaja tako da lijevo i desno uho su
in fact two different devices you can
u stvari dva različita uređaja možete
mount those to a phone or an mp3 player
montirajte ih na telefon ili mp3 plejer
that has Bluetooth or any device with
koji ima Bluetooth ili bilo koji uređaj sa
Bluetooth a computer even and you can
Bluetooth računar čak i možete
listen to your music in full beautiful
slušajte svoju muziku u punom sjaju
stereo with deep lows and nice crystal
stereo sa dubokim padovima i lepim kristalima
clear crisp treble but what that means
očistite jasne visoke tonove, ali šta to znači
to you is that you can also put this one
vama je da to možete staviti i na ovu
away and just use one right then you can
Odmaknite se i koristite samo jedan
actually use this one connected to a
zapravo koristi ovu povezanu na a
different device if you would like
drugi uređaj ako želite
so there are use cases you might be able
tako da postoje slučajevi upotrebe koji bi mogli biti u mogućnosti
to think of some places where
razmišljati o nekim mjestima gdje
that would be you know a neat neat idea
to bi bilo da znate urednu, urednu ideju
right certainly if you want to share you
pravo svakako ako želite da vas dijele
know if you want to use one and I'll use
Znaš ako želiš da ga koristiš, a ja ću koristiti
one if you're going on the motorcycle
jedan ako idete na motor
and you want to be able to talk with
i želite biti u mogućnosti da razgovaraju sa
Dave that's perfect there you go perfect
Dave koji je savršen tamo ideš savršen
okay so again we know doobies we know
U redu, opet znamo doubies znamo
how they do things we know how their
kako rade stvari koje znamo kako su njihove
chargers work this again comes with a
punjači rade ovo opet dolazi sa
nice little carrying case this one is a
Lepa mala torba za nošenje, ova je
belt clip model and we've got a little
model sa kopčom za remen i imamo malo
reveal here for the USB input to charge
otkrijte ovdje za USB ulaz za punjenje
the case can you imagine that you're
slučaj možete zamisliti da ste
charging the case then when we open that
zatim punjenje slučaju kada otvorimo da
up take your earbud and just set it
uzmite slušalicu i samo je postavite
right down in there done and just align
desno dole u tu uradi i samo uskladiti
that with the with the magnet there
to sa magnetom tamo
there we go
Evo idemo
close it down and turn it on there you
zatvorite ga i uključite tamo
go so now my earbuds are in fact
pa sada moje slušalice su zapravo
charging while they're not in use once
punjenje dok se ne koriste jednom
it's finished charging it'll stop
završilo se punjenje
charging and then the next time I open
punjenje, a zatim sledeći put kad otvorim
it up I pull out my earbuds they are
izvadim svoje slušalice
ready to go that's the jeebies beat wins
spremni za polazak, pobjeda pobjeda jeebija
so these both of these devices are
tako da ovi oba uređaja
absolutely exceptional so that we're
apsolutno izuzetna, tako da smo mi
seeing the evolution of earbuds here
vidimo evoluciju slušalica
folks if you're a music fan like myself
ako ste ljubitelj muzike kao ja
I absolutely love constantly listening
Apsolutno volim da stalno slušam
to music I've always got music playing I
za muziku sam uvek imao muziku I
love I actually use my laptop a lot with
ljubav sam zapravo koristiti moj laptop puno
Bluetooth and the be twins so it's not
Bluetooth i biti blizanci, tako da to nije
just for phones anymore so you can sync
samo za telefone, tako da možete sinhronizovati
it with your with your computer your
sa vašim sa vašim računarom
laptop your tablet your phone your mp3
vaš laptop tablet svoj telefon mp3
player my son has an mp3 player that has
igrač moj sin ima mp3 player koji ima
bluetooth so we use bluetooth on that
bluetooth tako da koristimo bluetooth na tome
and there you have it so any other
i tu ga imaš tako
points with the difference now oh the
bodova s ​​razlikom sada oh the
question is coming in about the price of
dolazi pitanje o ceni
the beat wins a little bit more regular
ritam osvaja malo redovnije
price is $99 again these are aluminum
cijena je $ 99 opet su aluminij
they're a little bit higher end
oni su malo viši kraj
certainly the drivers are upgraded so
sigurno su vozači tako nadograđeni
the sound quality on these is going to
kvaliteta zvuka na ovim će se
be probably I say probably I know this
verovatno kažem da znam ovo
is probably gonna be the best sounding
Verovatno će najbolje zvučati
year buddy you've ever heard be it wired
Godišnji prijatelj koga ste ikada čuli da je to bilo
or Wireless
ili Wireless
that's a fact this is the jeebies your
to je činjenica da je ovo vaš jeebies
be twins earbuds now at $99 that's a
budite blizanci u ušima sada na 99 dolara
steal but again cyber week this week if
kradem ali opet cyber nedelju ove nedelje ako
you're shopping right now for Christmas
trenutno kupujete za Božić
it's on sale for just $79.99 okay so
u prodaji je za samo 79,99 dolara
there you have it both come in multiple
tu imate obojicu u više navrata
different colors are there any points
različite boje postoje bilo koje tačke
that I've missed sash I think I I think
mislim da sam propustio pojas
you got it all Wow first shot I
Sve ste dobili
especially love because I ride my bike
posebno ljubav jer ja vozim svoj bicikl
right like a pedal bike a pedal bike
kao pedal bicikl
ride my bike in the spring summer and
vožnja biciklom u proljeće i ljeto
fall to and from the studio and I have
pasti na i iz studija i imam
like I had a like a bluetooth just like
kao da sam imao sličan bluetooth
earbud thing that I was using for fun
slušalice koje sam koristio za zabavu
and music kind of a yeah and that
i muzike vrsta da i to
doesn't sound anything like these I like
ne zvuči ništa slično ovome što mi se sviđa
the Google Maps just that tells me where
Google Maps samo mi govori gdje
to okay right so just in case you get
da se dobro okrenem za slučaj da dobiješ
lost on your way to the studio that
izgubljeni na putu do studija
you've been to a thousand times but the
bio si na hiljadu puta, ali
one that I was using and I mean it's
jedan koji sam koristio i mislim da je
just the typical one you would use right
samo onaj tipičan koji biste koristili
so it would always pop out and like
tako da bi se uvijek iskočilo i slično
these looks secure absolutely
ovo izgleda apsolutno sigurno
oh speaking of secure and you mentioned
Govorite o sigurnom i spomenuli ste
about the size of your ears so Sasha's
O veličinama tvojih ušiju tako da je Sašina
got the little ears I got the bigger
dobio sam male uši koje sam dobio
ones let's get into the box here of the
one hajdemo u kutiju ovdje u
B twins and see what else comes with it
B bliznakinje i vidite šta još dolazi sa njom
here we go okay some instruction manuals
idemo u redu nekoliko uputstava za upotrebu
some information there then we've got
Tamo imamo neke informacije
same thing we've got lots of different
ista stvar koju imamo mnogo drugačije
sizes there you go there's two more
Veličine eto ima još dva
these ones all have the these ones have
ovi svi imaju ove
that kind of flap that goes to hold it a
takva klapna koja ide da je drži a
little more solidly in your ear so it
malo više čvrsto u uho tako da
doesn't fall out when you're working out
ne ispada kada radite
and then we've got these ones do not so
i onda imamo ove ne
if you prefer not to have that you've
ako više ne želite da imate to
got that option we've got a registration
dobio sam tu opciju da imamo registraciju
card some information and a USB cable oh
neke informacije i USB kabl oh
and some more adapter things for the
i još nešto adaptera za
ears and the USB cable again is so that
i USB kabl je opet takav
you can charge the case so you never
možete naplatiti slučaj tako da nikada
chart you're never having to actually
grafikon ti nikada ne bi zapravo
plug in the earbuds themselves you're
sami priključite umetke za uši
charging the case and then you've got a
optužuje slučaj i onda imate
case here that will actually give you
ovde će vam to stvarno dati
about nine
oko devet
nine hours of charging so how do you
devet sati punjenja, pa kako ti ide
like that you can get these right now at
kao da to možete dobiti odmah
cat5 dot TV / headphones so make sure
cat5 dot TV / slušalice tako da budite sigurni
you check those out I absolutely loved
provjeravate one koje sam apsolutno volio
what Jimmy's is doing with with not only
s čim Jimmy radi ne samo
their ear buds but their entire product
njihove ušne pupoljke, ali čitav njihov proizvod
line we've looked at some of their
smo pogledali neke njihove
products here on the show before but
proizvode ovde na predstavi prije
definitely high-end quality absolutely
definitivno high-end kvalitete apsolutno
something that you want to pick up
nešto što želite da pokupi
easier Ricky cuz I didn't even know your
lakše Ricky cuz nisam ni znao tvoj
name they are nailing it the other point
ime su zakucavanje je druga stvar
with these is again I do need to
sa ovim je opet potrebno
reiterate just in case the question
ponovite samo u slučaju da se postavi pitanje
arises they are phone compatible so
nastaje da su telefonski kompatibilni
you're able to make and take calls with
moći ćete da pozivate i primate pozive
these you can control your phone you can
ove možete kontrolirati svoj telefon možete
talk to Siri you can talk to Google
razgovarajte sa Siri i možete razgovarati s Googleom
music called Google Google Voice Google
naziva Google Google Voice Google
Play Google now a new assistant yeah
Igrajte Google sada kao novi pomoćnik da
whatever the Google one is you know what
šta god da je Google , znate šta
I mean it will work for you having other
Mislim da će raditi za vas što drugi
colors they absolutely do both sets come
boje koje apsolutno rade oba seta
in various colors so check it out cat
u raznim bojama provjerite mačka
five dot TV / headphones
pet tačkastih TV / slušalica
[Music]
[Music] \ t
[Applause]
[Aplauz]